Open the door, room 214 My arms are full of bags
But I'm not the first one here Someone's in the
bed His pillows and his blankets he's already
fast asleep i must have the wrong room my heart
begins to
I check the card upon the door, my stomach's in a
knot Aubrey Jean Kelly, Madison Elizabeth
Scott And Aubrey Jordan Fuller, a clerical
mistake The boy in bed begins to stir, he's
starting to
He sits up and I see his eyes And I'm not scared at
all He just looks lost and terrified
He looks so small My mind just goes completely
clear A feeling I can't place
It's the first time that I've ever seen such
kindness
A new light's switching on
The noise outside the hallway is suddenly too
much He's rocking in his wheelchair, he's
trembling at my touch He's not angry, he's
overwhelmed, I know just what he needs He needs a
quiet anchor, a place where he can breathe
He sits up and I see his eyes And I'm not scared at
all He just looks lost and terrified
He looks so small. My mind just goes completely
clear.
This feeling I can't place. It's the first time
that I've ever seen such kindness.
A new light switching on
It's okay, focus on my voice.
You're safe.